https://www.fandango.com/policies/privacy-policy

Fandango
Screen Reader Users: To optimize your experience with your screen reading software, please use our Flixster.com website, which has the same tickets as our Fandango.com and MovieTickets.com websites.
Skip to Main Content
Go
Movies
Now Playing
See All Now Playing
Opening This Week
= Limited Release
Aggie (2020)
Henchmen
Pray: The Story of Patrick Peyton
The War with Grandpa
See All Opening This Week
Coming Soon
Honest Thief (2020)
Soul (2020)
Wonder Woman 1984
See All Coming Soon
Explore More
Watch Trailers on MovieClips
Top Box Office
New For Streaming
Theaters + Tickets
Where are you located? Here are our top cities
Read More
What to Watch on FandangoNOW: Disney’s ‘Mulan,’ RZA’s ‘Cut Throat City,’ Ruby Rose in ‘The Doorman’ and More
Read More
This Week in Movie News: Doctor Strange Joins ‘Spider-Man 3,’ Slinky Movie in the Works and More
Read More
Explore Content
Movie Reviews
Star Wars Guide
Awards Watch
Indie Movie Guide
Family Guide
House Of Screams
Weekend Ticket
My VIP Account
Join FandangoVIP
Buy Movies. Get Movies.
Earn 125 points on every ticket you buy. Rack up 500 points and you'll score a $5 reward for more movies.
Learn more
Insider Perks
Get your swag on with discounted movies to stream at home, exclusive movie gear, access to advanced screenings and discounts galore.
Learn more
Partner Rewards
Collect bonus rewards from our many partners, including AMC, Stubs, Cinemark Connections, Regal Crown Club when you link accounts.
Learn more
Refunds + Exchanges
We know life happens, so if something comes up, you can return or exchange your tickets up until the posted showtime.
Learn more
Join Fandango VIP For Free
(It only takes a few seconds to join)
Already a Fandango VIP? Sign In
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Terms and Policies
Terms of Use
Ticket Policy
Promo Code Policy
Gift Card Terms
Last updated: August 18, 2020
This Privacy Policy explains how Fandango Media, LLC and its subsidiary companies, including the businesses operating under the Fandango, FandangoNOW, Vudu, Rotten Tomatoes, Flixster,
Movieclips, Movies.com, Activaterewards.com, MovieTickets.com, or M-GO brands ("Fandango", "we", "our" or "us"), collect, use, and share information from or about you when you use our
websites, downloadable applications, interactive TV applications, voice-activated skills, other digital services, connected devices, and off-line services that link to this policy, or if you
generate ratings/reviews/public comments/content on our properties or engage in business with us (the “Services”). Note that this Privacy Policy does not apply to our movie ticketing business
that operates in Latin America, as that business has a separate privacy policy.
Our Owners
When the Services receive or collect information, that information is being received and collected, and will be owned, by Fandango and each of "Fandango's Owners" (i.e., each company that has
an ownership interest in Fandango). While Fandango's use, handling, disclosure and practices with respect to that information will be governed by this Privacy Policy, each Fandango’s Owners’
use, handling, disclosure and practices with respect to that information will be governed by that Fandango’s Owners’ privacy policy. Fandango's Owners are currently NBCUniversal and Warner
Bros. If you want to learn more about the privacy practices of NBCUniversal and Warner Bros., we encourage you to review their policies (linked below):
NBCUniversal Privacy Policy
Warner Bros. Privacy Policy
Your Rights to Dispute
Your use of our websites and our other services are subject to binding individual arbitration of any disputes which may arise, as provided in the Terms
and Policies. Please read the arbitration provisions of the Terms and Policies carefully and do not use the Services if you are unwilling to arbitrate any
disputes you may have with us as provided in our Terms and Policies.
PLEASE READ THIS PRIVACY POLICY CAREFULLY TO UNDERSTAND HOW WE HANDLE YOUR INFORMATION. BY USING THE SERVICES, YOU ACKNOWLEDGE YOU HAVE READ AND UNDERSTAND THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND THAT WE WILL
COLLECT, USE AND SHARE YOUR INFORMATION AS SET FORTH BELOW.
Table of Contents
Personal Information We Collect and Purposes
When We Share Your Information
Legal Bases For Use of Your Information
Children
Your Rights
Your Choices
How We Protect Your Information
International Transfers
Updates to Our Privacy Policy
Contact Us
1. PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT AND PURPOSES
The tables below explain the categories of information we collect and the purposes for which we use them. Please note that we may use any or all of this information to comply with the law,
detect or prevent fraud, and to defend our legal rights. Further detail about each of the purposes is set out in the “Additional information on purposes of use” table below.
Information you provide to us:
Categories of personal information we collect
Purposes of use
Contact information and account registration
For example: name, email, postal address, telephone number, account user name and password, business contact information, and any information you may provide to us at an
event or in person.
Provide the Services
Personalize your experience
Send you marketing communications
Provide seamless experience across platforms and devices
Protect our users, Services and properties
Build and manage business-to-business relationships
Market and advertise for third parties
Identification and demographics
For example: date of birth, gender, nationality, ethnicity, interests, lifestyle information, photos, social media credentials, including identification information about
friends, contacts or referrals you provide.
Provide the Services
Personalize your experience
Send you marketing communications
Provide seamless experience across platforms and devices
Protect our users, Services and properties
Market and advertise for third parties
Saved Preferences
For example: when you save on the Services your favorite theaters, favorite movies or genres, or city or zip code theater preferences.
Provide the Services
Personalize your experience
Send you marketing communications
Provide seamless experience across platforms and devices
Protect our users, Services and properties
Market and advertise for third parties
Transactional
For example: credit/debit card details, other payment details (e.g., PayPal, Venmo), purchase history, delivery address, membership information, reservations, loyalty
program memberships or subscriptions for companies or services other than Fandango, and the personal details of any of your guests.
Provide the Services
Personalize your experience
Send you marketing communications
Provide seamless experience across platforms and devices
Protect our users, Services and properties
Market and advertise for third parties
User-generated content
For example: photos, videos, audio, and other information you may submit to us, such as ratings/reviews or comments on our forums.
Provide the Services
Personalize your experience
Send you marketing communications
Provide seamless experience across platforms and devices
Protect our users, Services and properties
Market and advertise for third parties
Research and feedback
For example: comments that you send us through online forms and social media platforms, by email, over the phone, by mail, or in surveys.
Provide the Services
Personalize your experience
Send you marketing communications
Provide seamless experience across platforms and devices
Protect our users, Services and properties
Market and advertise for third parties
Biometric identifiers
For example: facial scans or fingerprints.
Provide the Services
Personalize your experience
Provide seamless experience across platforms and devices
Protect our users, Services and properties
Audio and video
For example: audio recordings of a customer service call or security video footage if you visit one of our properties.
Provide the Services
Personalize your experience
Protect our users, Services and properties
Information we collect automatically from you and/or your device:
Categories of personal information we collect
Purposes of use
Device information and identifiers
For example: IP address, cookie IDs, browser type and language, operating system, platform type, device type, and advertising and app identifiers.
Provide the Services
Personalize your experience
Send you marketing communications
Provide seamless experience across platforms and devices
Protect our users, Services and properties
Market and advertise for third parties
Connection and Usage
For example: domain names, browsing activity, scrolling and keystroke activity, theaters searched, locations searched, movies searched, shows viewed, movie trailers or
other advertisements viewed, forms or fields you complete or partially complete, search terms, whether you open an email, content you view and duration, quality of the
service and interaction with the content, logs, and other similar information. If these events occur while you are offline, they may be logged and uploaded to us when you
next connect.
Provide the Services
Personalize your experience
Send you marketing communications
Provide seamless experience across platforms and devices
Protect our users, Services and properties
Market and advertise for third parties
Geolocation
For example: city, state and ZIP code associated with your IP address or derived through Wi-Fi triangulation.
We will ask for your permission before using your precise location from GPS-based functionality on your mobile devices.
Provide the Services
Personalize your experience
Send you marketing communications
Provide seamless experience across platforms and devices
Protect our users, Services and properties
Market and advertise for third parties
Information we collect from third parties:
Categories of personal information we collect
Purposes of use
Sources of information
Information from public and commercial sources
For example: demographic and contact information, information about other members of your household, inferences about your preferences, loyalty program memberships or
subscriptions for companies or services other than Fandango, and purchasing data.
Provide the Services
Personalize your experience
Send you marketing communications
Provide seamless experience across platforms and devices
Build and manage business-to-business relationships
Market and advertise for third parties
Advertising providers
Analytics providers
Marketers
Partners (such as for sweepstakes partners)
Consumer data resellers
Public records databases
Social Media Information
For example: if you interact with us through a social media service or log in using social media credentials, depending on your social media settings, we may have access to
your information from that social network such as your name, email address, friend list, photo, age, gender, location, birthday, social networking ID, current city, your
comments about the Services, and the people/sites you follow.
Provide the Services
Personalize your experience
Send you marketing communications
Provide seamless experience across platforms and devices
Market and advertise for third parties
Social media networks
Partners of social media networks
Advertising providers
Analytics providers
Marketers
Partners (such as for sweepstakes partners)
Consumer data resellers
Additional information that we collect for business relationships only:
Categories of personal information we collect
Purposes of use
Sources of information
Business contact information
For example: company name, your name, email address, and job.
Build and manage business relationships
You
Your company
Trade associations
Social media
Business data resellers
Due diligence information
For example: contact information, nationality, job title, age, date of birth, gender, country of residence, employment and education information, public, religious,
political or trade union roles, personal and professional affiliations, connections to criminal activities or offenses related to money laundering.
Compliance and risk management activities for business relationships
Your or your company’s responses to our due diligence questions
Third party compliance screening tools and databases, such as those provided by LexisNexis Risk Solutions. Click here
for more information.
Additional information on purposes of use
Provide the Services, for example:
responding to your requests or inquiries, including technical support
sending you service-related communications
providing ticketing, payment services, mapping guidance, and offers
displaying content you generate, such as video and comments
carrying out research and analytics for uses including improving the Services and developing new ones
processing your information for promotional campaigns such as sweepstakes and contests, and for surveys, online and offline panels and focus groups
Personalize the experience, for example:
providing you with customized product experience, including personalized newsletters, viewing and other content recommendations from our partners and other
organizations.
providing you with advertising based on your activities and interests including at a household level
creating and updating profiles and audience segments that can be used for analytics, interest-based advertising and marketing on the Services, television, third party
services and platforms, mobile apps and/or websites, connected devices and offline
using inferences about your preferences and interests for any and all of the above purposes
Send marketing communications (with consent if required), for example:
sending you newsletters, surveys and information about products, services and promotions
Provide a seamless experience across platforms and devices, for example:
identifying you when you log into the Services on multiple devices or web browsers to provide continuity and to match your interests across devices for the purposes of
analytics, advertising, reporting and to improve the Services
identifying you if your devices have attributes suggesting that they may be used by the same individual or household for purposes of analytics, advertising, reporting
and to improve the Services
Build and manage business relationships, for example:
pursuing potential business opportunities, including identifying and contacting the correct person within the company
sending communications for business purposes
sending event invitations, marketing emails and campaigns, and tracking the effectiveness of such communications
providing business contacts with access to our systems, and managing that access
Market and advertise for third parties, for example:
send you newsletters, promotional emails, surveys and information about products, services and promotions offered by our partners and other organizations with which we
work
customize content that our third-party partners deliver on the Services (e.g., personalized third-party advertising)
create and update inferences about you and audience segments that can be used for interest-based advertising and marketing on the Services, third party services and
platforms, and mobile apps
create profiles about you, including adding and combining information we obtain from third parties and matching your interests across devices, which may be used for
third-party marketing and advertising on the Services, television, third party services and platforms, mobile apps and/or websites, connected devices and offline
Compliance and risk management activities for business relationships, for example:
compliance with laws and regulations
managing third party and other risks to our business
protecting the reputation of our businesses
following the principles of ethical business conduct set out in our Code of Conduct
Protect our users, Services and properties, for example:
protecting the safety and security of users and visitors to the Services
protecting our digital and physical properties
detecting and preventing other activities that may be illegal or in violation of our terms of service
We may combine all the information we collect from or receive about you for the outlined purposes. We may aggregate or deidentify your information and may use, share, rent or sell
aggregated or deidentified information for any purpose, and such information is not subject to this Privacy Policy.
Sale of Personal Information: If you, or someone acting on your behalf, would like to request that we do not sell your personal information, you can either click here for such request,
or send an email to donotsell@fandango.com. You will also need to clear your cookies and re-set your MAIDs, as referenced in the link. For more information about how to opt-out of
receiving targeted advertising from certain third party advertisers, please see our Cookies Notice.
For Vudu (which Fandango acquired from Walmart), if you are a California resident and you, or someone acting on your behalf, would like to request that Vudu does not sell your personal
information, you can either click here or call 800-925-6278 and Walmart will process your request on Vudu’s behalf.
2. WHEN WE SHARE YOUR INFORMATION
We may share your information with:
Theaters and Event Providers: We may share information so that they may admit you, or address customer service issues at the theater or venue, or help process your
ticketing or transactions, or otherwise to fulfill the Services.
Advertisers, Advertising Networks, and Other Third Parties: We may share information about how you use the Services and interact with content or ads to better tailor
services, products, marketing and advertising on the Services and on third-party platforms. To enable these purposes, we may share certain demographics information, user-generated
content, device information and identifiers, connection and usage data, geolocation data, public and commercial information, and social media information. These third parties may use
their own tracking technologies to collect or request information about you, please see our Cookies Notice.
Partners: We may share your information with third party partners. For instance, if you enter a contest, promotion or sweepstakes sponsored by a third party, we may
share the information you provide for that entry with the sponsor. Depending on the partnership, we may share certain information including contact information (at your direction),
identification and demographic information, transactional information, user-generated content that you provide, research and feedback, device information and identifiers, connection
and usage information, public and commercial information, and social media information. We may also share your information with third parties that provide video locker services if you
purchase a movie or other show to view at home. Examples of such a third party would be Movies Anywhere. Similarly, we may share your information with the providers of loyalty
programs if you take an action in the Services indicating that you would like to obtain a benefit under such a program through activity on the Services.
Social Networks: We may share your information with social media platforms for example, if you click on a Facebook “like” button on the Services, the “like” may
appear on your Facebook account. To control this sharing of information, please review and adjust your privacy settings for the relevant social network. Depending on your privacy
settings and actions on such network, we may share contact information, identification and demographic information, user-generated content, device information and identifiers,
connection and usage data, and social media information.
Service Providers: We engage vendors to perform services for business purposes on our behalf and share information with them to enable them to provide us with such
services, including research and analytics, hosting, transaction and payment processing, promotion administration, fraud prevention, identity management, acquisition and other
services. Service providers may use such information for their operational purposes in order to provide their services to us.
Research and Measurement Companies: We may share information about content you view on the Services with video measurement services such as Nielsen TV
Ratings, as well as other analytics providers. See Your Rights and Your Choices sections for more information.
Search Engines: You may be able to engage with other members of the Services or the public. This may make the name and photo associated with your profile and any
comments or user-generated content you provide visible to other members of the Services or the general public. If the information is available to the general public, it may also be
searchable by search engines.
Law Enforcement, Regulators, Anti-fraud Coalitions and Other Groups: We share any of the categories of information we collect, as appropriate, with these third
parties in order to: protect and enforce the legal rights, privacy, and safety of ourselves and our visitors; protect against possible fraud or other illegal activity; respond to
requests from government and other authorities; and otherwise comply with legal process.
Other Sharing: We may share information about you, often along with a hashed or masked identifier, with third parties so they may better personalize your experience
with them and the advertising and other offers they show or otherwise send you and to determine advertising effectiveness. With your appropriate consent when required, and consistent
with applicable law, we may share your video viewing behavior with third parties including service providers, advertising companies, analytics partners, and social media sites.
Sale or Transfer of All or Part of Our Business or Assets: In the event that Fandango (or any Fandango business) is involved in a merger, acquisition, transfer of
control, bankruptcy, reorganization or sale of assets, or diligence associated with such matters, we may sell or transfer the information described in this Privacy Policy as part of
that transaction.
Sale of Personal Information: Under California law, certain of the information sharing described above may be categorized as the “sale” of “personal information”
under certain circumstances. California law broadly defines “sale” in a way that may include allowing third parties to receive certain information such as cookies, IP address and/or
browsing behavior to add to a profile about your device, browser, or you. This profile may enable delivery of interest-based advertising on the Services or other sites. Depending on
what Services you use, we may share the following categories of information for such advertising which may be considered a sale (as defined by California law): identification and
demographics; device information and identifiers, such as IP address, and unique advertising identifiers and cookies; connection and usage information, such as browsing history or app
usage; geolocation information, such as city; and inference data. To the extent that it does constitute such a “sale”, you may opt out of that sale through the mechanism described
below.
3. LEGAL BASES FOR USE OF YOUR INFORMATION
Laws other than the federal, state and local laws of the United States do not apply to our watch-at-home movie Services (e.g., FandangoNOW/M-GO and Vudu) as content from those Services can
be viewed only in the United States. Similarly, for our movie ticketing Services (e.g., Flixster, Fandango.com and MovieTickets.com), the only laws that shall apply are the laws of the
countries in which the theaters ticketed by each respective Service are located. The information set forth below in this section is applicable only to European Users of Rotten Tomatoes.
It supplements certain sections of this Privacy Policy and provides additional information that should be read together with other sections of this Privacy Policy. To the extent there is
any conflict between this section and another section of this Privacy Policy, this section shall govern.
When this policy mentions "Fandango", "we", "our" or "us", it refers to the company or companies responsible for your information under this Privacy Policy (or “Data Controller”). This
includes Fandango Media, LLC and Fandango’s Owners (as defined above), currently NBCUniversal, LLC and Warner Bros (please see above for further information on these companies).
The laws of some jurisdictions, such as the European Union, require companies to tell you about the legal basis for using, sharing, or disclosing your information. To the extent those laws
apply, we may rely on the following legal bases:
Performance of a contract: where use of your information is necessary to provide you with the Services under a contract, for example the terms of service.
Legitimate interest: where use of your information is necessary for our or others’ legitimate interests and where the use is not outweighed by your rights and
interests. Below are some examples of such interests:
providing the Services
improving the Services and developing new ones
recognizing and better understanding our users, including across platforms
conducting security and fraud prevention activities
marketing and promoting our content and services
building and managing business relationships
conducting compliance and risk management activities
providing and managing access to our systems
Legal obligation: where use of your information is necessary to comply with laws and regulations such as those relating to anti-bribery and corruption and
anti-money-laundering, complying with requests from government bodies or courts, or responding to litigation.
With consent: we may ask for your consent to process your information in a certain way. Where we rely on this basis, you have the right to withdraw your consent at
any time – please see the Your Rights and Your Choices sections below to do this.
How Long We Keep Your Information
We will keep your information only for as long as it is necessary to fulfill the purposes described above, unless a longer retention is required or permitted by law. We may delete or
de-identify your information sooner if we receive a verifiable deletion request, subject to exemptions under applicable law. The retention period that applies to your information may vary
depending on the Services you use and how you interact with them.
4. CHILDREN
The Services are not designed or intended for use by children under 13, and thus if you are under 13 we ask that you do not use the Services or provide us with any information. If we
discover that we have inadvertently gathered any such information then we will, to the extent required by law, delete such information from our records. There is one exception to this: we
may offer a Service that is directed to children under the age of 13, and if we do it will state that it collects information from children, and it will also have a separate privacy
policy posted detailing the practices specific to that Service. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child under 13 has provided us with information without his or her
consent, he or she should contact us at privacy@fandango.com.
5. YOUR RIGHTS
Depending on where you live, you may have certain rights with respect to your information. For example, under local laws, you may be able to ask us to:
provide access to certain information we hold about you, in some cases in a portable format, if technically feasible
update or correct your information
delete certain information
restrict the use of your information
We will respond within the time period prescribed by applicable law. Please note that many of the above rights are subject to exceptions and limitations. You have the right not to be
discriminated against (as provided for in applicable law) for exercising your rights under some local laws such as in California.
Some Services can be provided only if we have your information, therefore deletion of your information will result in termination of such Services.
We will take reasonable steps to verify your identity, including authenticating you through the email address we have on file. We may require further documentation such as a password and
user ID before granting access to your information. As you may be aware, we recently acquired Vudu from Walmart, and Walmart is still providing certain privacy related services for Vudu,
including fulfilling California Consumer Privacy Act (“CCPA”) requests to the extent required by law.
You may submit the following types of requests as follows:
Request Categories of Information: If you, or someone acting on your behalf, would like to request that we tell you the categories of personal
information we collect, the categories of sources from which personal information is collected, the business or commercial purpose for collecting or selling the personal information,
the categories of third parties with which the business shares personal information, the categories of information about you that we sell, the categories of third parties to whom the
personal information was sold, or the categories of personal information that were disclosed for a business purpose, you or someone acting on your behalf can either click here for such request, or send
an email to accessdata@fandango.com.
As you may be aware, we recently acquired Vudu from Walmart, and Walmart is still providing certain privacy related services for Vudu, including
fulfilling CCPA requests to the extent required by law. If you are a California resident and you, or someone acting on your behalf, would like to request that Vudu tell you
the categories of personal information Vudu collects, the categories of sources from which personal information is collected, the business or commercial purpose for collecting
or selling the personal information, the categories of third parties with which Vudu shares personal information, the categories of information about you that Vudu sells, the
categories of third parties to whom the personal information was sold, or the categories of personal information that were disclosed for a business purpose, you or someone
acting on your behalf can either click here or call 800-925-6278 and Walmart will process
your request on Vudu’s behalf.
Request Specific Information: If you, or someone acting on your behalf, would like to request that we tell you about some of the specific personal
information that we hold about you, you or someone acting on your behalf can either click here for such request, or send
an email to accessdata@fandango.com.
As you may be aware, we recently acquired Vudu from Walmart, and Walmart is still providing certain privacy related services for Vudu, including
fulfilling CCPA requests to the extent required by law. If you are a California resident and you, or someone acting on your behalf, would like to request that Vudu tell you
about some of the specific personal information that Vudu holds about you, you or someone acting on your behalf can either click here or call 800-925-6278 and Walmart will process your request on Vudu’s behalf.
Request Deletion: If you, or someone acting on your behalf, would like to request that we delete information that we hold about you, you or someone
acting on your behalf can either click
here for such request, or send an email to deletedata@fandango.com. Note that certain information about you will not be deleted if
you request such a deletion, as may be permitted by law. Also note that we will not be able to provide you with certain Services upon a deletion. You will also need to clear your
cookies and re-set your MAIDs, as referenced in the link.
As you may be aware, we recently acquired Vudu from Walmart, and Walmart is still providing certain privacy related services for Vudu, including
fulfilling CCPA requests to the extent required by law. If you are a California resident and you, or someone acting on your behalf, would like to request that Vudu deletes
information that Vudu holds about you, you or someone acting on your behalf can either click
here or call 800-925-6278 and Walmart will process your request on Vudu’s behalf.
Do Not Sell My Personal Information: If you, or someone acting on your behalf, would like to request that we do not sell your personal information, you
or someone acting on your behalf can either click here for such request, or send an email to donotsell@fandango.com. You will also need to clear your cookies and re-set your MAIDs, as referenced in the link. For more information
about how to opt-out of receiving targeted advertising from certain third party advertisers, please see our Cookies Notice.
As you may be aware, we recently acquired Vudu from Walmart, and Walmart is still providing certain privacy related services for Vudu, including
fulfilling CCPA requests to the extent required by law. If you are a California resident and you, or someone acting on your behalf, would like to request that Vudu does not
sell your personal information, you or someone acting on your behalf can either click here or
call 800-925-6278 and Walmart will process your request on Vudu’s behalf.
Please note that you may be located in a jurisdiction where we are not obligated, or are unable, to fulfill a request. In such a case, your request may not be fulfilled. In addition, the
above requests do not apply to Fandango’s Owners, who are currently NBCUniversal and Warner Bros. To send them requests, please visit their websites.
If you have any unresolved concerns, you may have the right to complain to your local data protection authority.
Additional Rights for California Residents: Residents of the State of California may request a list of all third parties to which the Services have disclosed certain personal information
(as defined by California law) during the preceding year for those third parties' direct marketing purposes. If you are a California resident and want such a list, please contact us at
Fandango, Attn: Privacy Officer, 407 N. Maple Dr., Suite 300, Beverly Hills, CA 90210. For all requests, you must put the statement "Your California Privacy Rights" in the body of your
request, as well as your name, street address, city, state, and zip code. In the body of your request, please provide enough information for us to determine if this applies to you. You
need to attest to the fact that you are a California resident and provide a current California address for our response. Please note that we will not accept requests via the telephone,
email, or by facsimile, and we are not responsible for notices that are not labeled or sent properly, or that do not have complete information.
6. YOUR CHOICES
Cookies and Similar Technologies
We and our service providers, advertisers, and other third parties use cookies and similar technologies (e.g., HTTP cookies, HTML 5, flash local storage cookies, web beacons, GIFs,
embedded scripts, ETags/cache browsers, and software development kits) to recognize you on, off, and across the Services and your devices. For more information about the use of cookies
and similar technologies on the Services (including your opt-out choices) please see our Cookies Notice.
Mobile App and Connected Devices
Depending on the device you use, you may be able to manage your advertising and location preferences through your device settings and as outlined in our Cookies
Notice. Many operating systems provide their own instructions on how to prevent the delivery of tailored in-application
advertisements. We do not control how the applicable platform operator allows you to manage personalized in-application advertisements. You should review your device manufacturer’s
support materials and/or the device settings for the respective operating systems for more detail on how to manage such preferences.
You may opt out of location data collection on our mobile app(s) by managing your location preferences in the "My Account" section of that app, or by disabling the GPS services for that
app on your mobile device. Contact privacy@fandango.com for information about how to opt out from allowing us to have further access to your
precise location data. Please include as much detail as possible when you make a request.
You can stop all collection of information by a mobile app by uninstalling the app.
Third-Party Online Services
The Services may contain links to third party services. These other sites (even if co-branded as Fandango) may collect information about you and use this information in accordance with
their own privacy policies and terms of service. We do not control those third parties’ policies or practices. Where Fandango collects personal information on a co-branded website or
service, we will provide a link to our privacy policy as appropriate. In some circumstances, we may host some websites on behalf of others and those entities may place or permit the
placement of cookies and other tracking technology. We are not responsible for these tracking practices.
Google Maps
If you use Google Maps / Google Earth as part of the Services, you agree to comply with the Google Maps / Google Earth Additional Terms of Service (including the Google
Privacy Policy). Further, you agree that Google, and not Fandango, shall be responsible for any of your information Google
receives as a result of your use of Google Maps / Google Earth.
7. HOW WE PROTECT YOUR INFORMATION
We maintain organizational, technical, and physical safeguards to help protect the information we collect and use. These safeguards vary depending upon a variety of factors including the
sensitivity of the information we collect and use. Despite all reasonable practices, no security method is infallible.
8. INTERNATIONAL TRANSFERS
Fandango is a global company and has its headquarters in the United States. We may transfer your information to those described in this Privacy Policy outside of your country of residence,
including in the United States and other countries. This is necessary to provide the Services and for the purposes outlined in this Privacy Policy. Data privacy laws vary from country to
country and they may not be equivalent to, or as protective as, the laws in your home country. We take steps to ensure that reasonable safeguards are in place with an aim to ensure an
appropriate level of protection for your information, in accordance with applicable law. By providing us with your information, you acknowledge any such transfer, storage or use.
9. UPDATES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY
We reserve the right to amend this Privacy Policy at any time to reflect changes to our practices or the law. We will make the revised Privacy Policy accessible through the Services.
Please check the Services periodically for updates.
The date at the top of this Privacy Policy tells you when it was last updated. If we make material changes to the way we collect or use your information, you will be provided with
appropriate notice, including, but not limited to, by posting the updated Privacy Policy on this website, and providing notice in accordance with legal requirements. Any changes to this
Privacy Policy will become effective when the revised Privacy Policy is posted. By continuing to use the Services following any changes to this Privacy Policy, you acknowledge you have
read and understand the updated Privacy Policy, and you understand that we will collect, use, and share information as stated therein.
10. CONTACT US
For any questions in relation to this Privacy Policy please contact us at privacy@fandango.com or Fandango, ATTN: Legal Department, 407 N. Maple
Dr., Suite 300, Beverly Hills, CA 90210.
We have separate policies for workforce data, which is governed by the policies of our parent company, NBCUniversal. For example, please see the Candidate
Privacy Statement to find out more about the information collected during our recruitment process.
Offers
Get $5 Off Towards a Movie Download
when you purchase 3 participating Suave products 9/1-10/31 at Walmart or Walmart.com.
Unhinged (2020)
Thanks for signing up!
Fandango Affiliated Companies:
Fandango helps you go back to the movies with confidence and peace of mind.
